darbysmart.com 2016-06-20

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.darbysmart.com and Darby Smart, Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Darby Smart include www.darbysmart.com and Darby Smart, Inc. The Darby Smart website is an ecommerce site. By using the Darby Smart website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

### Collection of your Personal Information

Darby Smart may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Darby Smart's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Darby Smart. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Darby Smart website. 

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Darby Smart's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. 

Darby Smart encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Darby Smart so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Darby Smart is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Darby Smart website. 

### Use of your Personal Information

Darby Smart collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. 

Darby Smart may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Darby Smart and its affiliates. Darby Smart may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

### Darby Smart does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Darby Smart may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Darby Smart, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

Darby Smart may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Darby Smart, in order to determine what Darby Smart services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Darby Smart to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

Darby Smart will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Darby Smart or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Darby Smart; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Darby Smart, or the public. 

### Promotions

Darby Smart Referral Program - We reserve the right to refuse sales to anyone. On all orders related to our referral program, valid referrals are defined as a new Darby Smart customer in a unique household.

### Use of Cookies

The Darby Smart website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Darby Smart pages, or register with Darby Smart site or services, a cookie helps Darby Smart to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Darby Smart website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Darby Smart features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Darby Smart services or websites you visit. 

### Security of your Personal Information

Darby Smart secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

### Children Under Thirteen

Darby Smart does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Darby Smart by contacting us here: [wink@darbysmart.com](mailto:wink@darbysmart.com)

### Changes to this Statement

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy for the Site, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Any changes will be consistent with the stated Principles of the Safe Harbor Agreement. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted. Please check this page periodically for changes to this Privacy Policy. 

### Contact Information

Darby Smart welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Darby Smart has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us at: 

Darby Smart, Inc   
290 8th St.   
San Francisco, California 94103   
United States of America   

Our Site is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Site, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy. 

### Effective Date

This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on May 10, 2013.
